Guide to the Frank Moore Papers, 1971-2003 MSS.135
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Art Files, 153303
  - Subseries C: Frank Moore Miscellaneous Fragments, 153453
    - Materials taken from Monet: Water-lilies, undated; 153471 (Box 10, Folder 400)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198695 (Box 10, Folder 401)
    - Materials taken from The Myth of Freedom and the Way of Meditation, undated; 153470 (Box 10, Folder 402)
    - Notes regarding Travel in Spain, undated; 153469 (Box 10, Folder 403)
    - Materials taken from P.H. Emerson, Photographer of New York, undated; 153468 (Box 10, Folder 404)
    - Materials taken from Pacific: An Undersea Journey, undated; 153467 (Box 10, Folder 405)
    - Materials taken from Post-Impressionism from Van Gogh to Gaug, undated; 153466 (Box 10, Folder 406)
    - Materials taken from Revised Standard Version, Bible, undated; 153465 (Box 10, Folder 407)
    - Materials taken from The Sewanee Review, undated; 153464 (Box 10, Folder 408)
    - Materials taken from The Shell Book, 1972; 153463 (Box 10, Folder 409)
    - Materials taken from The Slipper Orchids, undated; 153462 (Box 10, Folder 410)
    - Materials taken from Surviving with AIDS by C. Wayne Collouray M.D., undated; 153461 (Box 10, Folder 411)
    - Materials taken from Tony Feher Siempre Contigo, undated; 153460 (Box 10, Folder 412)
    - Materials taken from A Treasury of Western Folklore, undated; 153459 (Box 10, Folder 413)
    - Materials taken from Views from the Real World, Early Tales, undated; 153458 (Box 10, Folder 414)
    - Materials taken from Weird adn Wonderful Ants, undated; 153457 (Box 10, Folder 415)
    - Materials taken from Wild, Wild World of Animals: Insects and Spiders, undated; 153456 (Box 10, Folder 416)
    - Materials taken from Zen Painting, undated; 153455 (Box 10, Folder 417)
    - Miscellaneous notes and papers, undated; 153454 (Box 10, Folder 418)
  - Subseries D: Other Artists, 153304
    - Acheson, Peter, 1988; 153452 (Box 10, Folder 419)
    - Ahearn, John, 1998; 153451 (Box 10, Folder 420)
    - Alvez, Justino, 1977; 153450 (Box 10, Folder 421)
    - Anderson, Curtis, 1985-1998; 153449 (Box 10, Folder 422)
    - Armitage Ballet, 1987; 153448 (Box 10, Folder 424)
    - Atlas, Charles, ca. 1980; 153447 (Box 10, Folder 425)
    - B., Beth, 1991-1995; 153446 (Box 10, Folder 426)
    - Baldessari, John, 1980; 153445 (Box 10, Folder 427)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer, 1985; 153444 (Box 10, Folder 428)
    - Bartos, Adam, 1988-1991; 153443 (Box 10, Folder 429)
    - Basquiat, Jean Michel, undated; 153442 (Box 10, Folder 430)
    - Bergtold, Susanna, 1996; 153441 (Box 10, Folder 431)
    - Blane, Marc, ca. 1988; 153440 (Box 10, Folder 432)
    - Bonechi, Lorenzo, 1993; 153439 (Box 10, Folder 433)
    - Boodro, Michael, 1980; 153438 (Box 10, Folder 434)
    - Bosman, Richard, 1986; 153437 (Box 10, Folder 435)
    - Brainard, Joe, 1964-1992; 153436 (Box 10, Folder 436)
    - Broida, Edward R., 1998; 153435 (Box 10, Folder 437)
    - Calder, 1994; 153434 (Box 10, Folder 438)
    - Chaet, Bernard, 1975-1998; 153433 (Box 10, Folder 440)
    - Chagall, Marc, 1982; 153432 (Box 10, Folder 441)
    - Chermann, Jean-Francois, 1997; 153431 (Box 10, Folder 442)
    - Chi, Tseng Kwong, undated; 153430 (Box 10, Folder 443)
    - Clay, Langdon, 1983; 153429 (Box 10, Folder 444)
    - Combas, Robert, 1985; 153428 (Box 10, Folder 445)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198686 (Box 10, Folder 446)
    - Connelly, Arch, 1983-1984; 153427 (Box 10, Folder 447)
    - Craig-Martin, Michael, 1999-2000; 153426 (Box 10, Folder 448)
    - Cross, Dorothy, 1995; 153425 (Box 10, Folder 449)
    - Dart, Joanna Pousette, 1995; 153424 (Box 10, Folder 450)
    - Delahunty, undated; 153423 (Box 10, Folder 451)
    - Dellavedova, Mario, undated; 153422 (Box 10, Folder 452)
    - Desert, Jn. Ulrick, 2000; 153421 (Box 10, Folder 453)
    - Dickson, Jane, 1986; 153420 (Box 10, Folder 454)
    - Dlugos, Tim, undated; 153419 (Box 10, Folder 455)
    - Dole, William, 1976; 153418 (Box 10, Folder 456)
    - Driver, Sara, 1981; 153417 (Box 10, Folder 457)
    - Dugdale, John, 1994-1999; 153416 (Box 10, Folder 458)
    - E., Ethyl, 1980; 153415 (Box 10, Folder 459)
    - Elmslie, Kenward, 1998; 153414 (Box 10, Folder 460)
    - Episalla, Joy, 1996-2001; 153413 (Box 10, Folder 461)
    - de Fazio, John [additional materials in oversize box], 19992-1994; 153412 (Box 10, Folder 462)
    - Feher, Tony, 1995; 153411 (Box 10, Folder 463)
    - Frame, Allen [additional materials in oversize box], 1990-1996; 153410 (Box 10, Folder 464)
    - Friedman, Dan, 1984; 153409 (Box 10, Folder 465)
    - Fulton, Hamish, undated; 153408 (Box 10, Folder 466)
    - Futura 2000, undated; 153407 (Box 10, Folder 467)
    - Garbe, William, 1980; 153406 (Box 10, Folder 468)
    - Gober, Robert, 1985-1994; 153405 (Box 10, Folder 469)
    - Goldin, Nan, ca. 1994; 153404 (Box 10, Folder 470)
    - Graham, Dan, undated; 153403 (Box 10, Folder 471)
    - Green, Elliot, undated; 153402 (Box 10, Folder 472)
    - Green, Gregory, 1998; 153401 (Box 10, Folder 473)
    - Guilliatt, Lee, undated; 153400 (Box 10, Folder 474)
    - Gundersen, Bruce, 1997; 153399 (Box 10, Folder 475)
    - Gunderson, Greta, 1989; 153398 (Box 10, Folder 476)
    - Hammond, Jane, 1993-1995; 153397 (Box 10, Folder 477)
    - Handorff, Joel, 1984; 153396 (Box 10, Folder 478)
    - Hannah, Duncan, 1994; 153395 (Box 10, Folder 479)
    - Haring, Keith, 1981-1999; 153394 (Box 10, Folder 480)
    - Harte, Glynn Boyd [additional materials located in oversize box], 1979-1987; 153393 (Box 10, Folder 481)
    - Hashey, Jan, 1984-19988; 153392 (Box 10, Folder 482)
    - Hawkins, Robert, ca. 1987; 153391 (Box 10, Folder 483)
    - Hawkins, William L., 1997; 153390 (Box 10, Folder 484)
    - Hayden, Victor, 1991; 153389 (Box 10, Folder 485)
    - Henderson, Edward, 1981; 153388 (Box 10, Folder 486)
    - Henry, Janet, 1995; 153387 (Box 10, Folder 487)
    - Hodermarsky, Maria, undated; 153386 (Box 10, Folder 488)
    - Horn, Richard, undated; 153385 (Box 10, Folder 489)
    - Hujar, Peter, 1987; 153384 (Box 10, Folder 490)
    - Hull, Greg, undated; 153383 (Box 10, Folder 491)
    - Humphrey, David, 1993-1998; 153382 (Box 10, Folder 492)
    - Hunter, Francine, 1993; 153381 (Box 10, Folder 493)
    - Michael, Hurson, 1989-1991; 153380 (Box 10, Folder 494)
    - Juarez, Roberto, 1981-1994; 153379 (Box 10, Folder 495)
    - Kardon, Dennis, ca. 1996; 153378 (Box 10, Folder 496)
    - Kelly, John a.k.a. Dogmar Onassis, 1987-1991; 153377 (Box 10, Folder 497)
    - Kennard, John, 1987; 153376 (Box 10, Folder 498)
    - Kortick, Roy, 1998; 153375 (Box 10, Folder 499)
    - Kramer, Larry, 1992; 153374 (Box 10, Folder 500)
    - LeDray, Charles, undated; 153373 (Box 10, Folder 501)
    - Leibowitz, Cary, 1990; 153372 (Box 10, Folder 502)
    - Longendyke, Paula, undated; 153371 (Box 10, Folder 503)
    - Lukacs, Attila Richard, 1989; 153370 (Box 10, Folder 504)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198687 (Box 10, Folder 505)
    - McClatchy, J.D., undated; 153369 (Box 10, Folder 506)
    - Marten, Ruth, 1997; 153368 (Box 10, Folder 507)
    - Martin, Chris, 1988-1995; 153367 (Box 10, Folder 508)
    - Melle, undated; 153366 (Box 10, Folder 509)
    - Metz, Mike, 1991; 153365 (Box 10, Folder 510)
    - Miller, Steve, 1982-1993; 153364 (Box 10, Folder 511)
    - Milow, Keith, ca. 1993; 153363 (Box 10, Folder 512)
    - Minagawa, Yasuo, undated; 153362 (Box 10, Folder 513)
    - Miro, Joan, 1983-1985; 153361 (Box 10, Folder 514)
    - Morper, Daniel, 1986; 153360 (Box 10, Folder 515)
    - Mueller, Cookie [additional materials in oversize box], undated; 153359 (Box 10, Folder 516)
    - Mueller, Stephen, 1994; 153358 (Box 10, Folder 517)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198688 (Box 10, Folder 518)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1995; 153357 (Box 10, Folder 519)
    - Nechvatal, Joseph, 1990; 153356 (Box 10, Folder 520)
    - Negroponte, George, 1985-1998; 153355 (Box 10, Folder 521)
    - Nelson, Joan, 1995; 153354 (Box 10, Folder 522)
    - Neshat, Shirin, 1999; 153353 (Box 10, Folder 523)
    - O'Connor, Tere, 1993; 153352 (Box 10, Folder 524)
    - Oji, Helen, 1995; 153351 (Box 10, Folder 525)
    - Ontani, Luigi, 1994; 153350 (Box 10, Folder 526)
    - Osorio, Pepon, 1991-1996; 153349 (Box 10, Folder 527)
    - Otterness, Tom, 1982-1985; 153348 (Box 10, Folder 528)
    - Pines, Lisa, 1996; 153347 (Box 10, Folder 529)
    - Potterat, Anne-Francoise, undated; 153346 (Box 10, Folder 530)
    - Pousette-Dart, Joanna, 1983; 153345 (Box 10, Folder 531)
    - Pozzi, Lucio, 1990-1991; 153344 (Box 10, Folder 532)
    - Rand, Archie, 1991; 153343 (Box 10, Folder 533)
    - Rhein, Eric, 1998; 153342 (Box 10, Folder 534)
    - Riopelle, Jean-Paul, 1987-1989; 153341 (Box 10, Folder 535)
    - Rockman, Alexis, undated; 153340 (Box 10, Folder 536)
    - Rosen, Jane, 1993; 153339 (Box 10, Folder 537)
    - Rosenquist, James, 1998; 153338 (Box 10, Folder 538)
    - Salerno, Linda, undated; 153337 (Box 10, Folder 539)
    - Santore, Joseph, 1990; 153336 (Box 10, Folder 540)
    - Sarfati, Patrick [additional items located in oversize box], 1978-1984; 153335 (Box 10, Folder 541)
    - Sovinio, Alberto, 1995; 153334 (Box 10, Folder 542)
    - Scharf, Kenny, ca. 1995; 153333 (Box 10, Folder 543)
    - Schlesinger, Peter, 1997; 153332 (Box 10, Folder 544)
    - Self, Jim [additional materials in oversize box], 1981-2000; 153331 (Box 10, Folder 545)
    - Self, Jim. Cunningham Studio June-July 1980, 153330 (Box 10, Folder 546)
    - Self, Jim. Dance Theater Workshop. Fall 1980, 153329 (Box 10, Folder 547)
    - Self, Jim. Jacob's Pillow, undated; 153328 (Box 10, Folder 548)
    - Self, Jim at MoMA, 1980; 153327 (Box 10, Folder 549)
    - Seymour, Dermot, 1989; 153326 (Box 10, Folder 550)
    - Shaver, Nancy, 1994; 153325 (Box 10, Folder 551)
    - Shils, E.B., undated; 153324 (Box 10, Folder 552)
    - Simons, Tom, undated; 153323 (Box 10, Folder 553)
    - Slaughter, Tom, 1996; 153322 (Box 10, Folder 554)
    - Smith, Gregory, 1987; 153321 (Box 10, Folder 555)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198689 (Box 10, Folder 556)
    - Smith, Philip, 1998; 153320 (Box 10, Folder 557)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198690 (Box 10, Folder 558)
    - Stalin, John, 1982; 153319 (Box 10, Folder 559)
    - Steers, Hugh, 1993-1998; 153318 (Box 10, Folder 560)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198691 (Box 10, Folder 561)
    - Stoll, George, 1994-1998; 153317 (Box 10, Folder 562)
    - Taylor, Steed, 1996; 153316 (Box 10, Folder 563)
    - Tisa, Ken, 1981; 153315 (Box 10, Folder 564)
    - Tuttle, Richard, 1998; 153314 (Box 10, Folder 566)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198692 (Box 10, Folder 567)
    - Warhol, Andy, 1995; 153313 (Box 10, Folder 568)
    - Warren, Rosanna [additional materials in oversize box], 1984-1995; 153312 (Box 10, Folder 569)
    - Winokur, Neil [additional materials in oversize box], 1982-1989; 153311 (Box 10, Folder 570)
    - Winters, Robin, 1993; 153310 (Box 10, Folder 571)
    - Wojnarowicz, David [additional materials in oversize box], ca. 1989; 153309 (Box 11, Folder 572)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042232499
    - Woodruf, Thomas, 1991-1999; 153308 (Box 11, Folder 573)
    - Wootton, Cynthia, 1983; 153307 (Box 11, Folder 574)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198693 (Box 11, Folder 575)
    - Group shows, performances, projects and events, undated; 153306 (Box 11, Folder 576)
    - Miscellaneous [additional materials in oversize box], undated; 153305 (Box 11, Folder 577)
- Series III: Correspondence and Manuscripts, 153140
  This series includes correspondence, primarily documents written to Moore and manuscripts. The series is organized into four subseries; A: Last Names, subseries B: First Name Only, subseries C: Miscellaneous, Illegible or Unindicated and subseries D: Manuscripts. Materials in this series are organized alphabetically.
  - Subseries A: Last Name, 153185
    - Item removed to oversize, 198685 (Box 11, Folder 578)
    - Alago, Michael, 1994; 153302 (Box 11, Folder 579)
    - Andrews, Frank, 1982; 153301 (Box 11, Folder 580)
    - Atkins, Shawn of House of Frame by Frame Fierce., 2001; 153300 (Box 11, Folder 581)
    - Berg, Henry, 1975; 153299 (Box 11, Folder 582)
    - Bergtold, Amy, 1992; 153298 (Box 11, Folder 583)
    - Bergtold, Paul, 1993; 153297 (Box 11, Folder 584)
    - Bibo, James Stuart, 1998; 153296 (Box 11, Folder 585)
    - Bishop, James, 1980-1983; 153295 (Box 11, Folder 586)
    - Blane, Marc, 1988-1991; 153294 (Box 11, Folder 587)
    - Brainard, Joe, 1988-1993; 153293 (Box 11, Folder 588)
    - Buddhayana, ca. 1996; 153292 (Box 11, Folder 589)
    - Bush, Bob, 1975; 153291 (Box 11, Folder 590)
    - Cadmus, Paul, 1982-1998; 153290 (Box 11, Folder 591)
    - Carriere, Jennifer and Mathieu, 1985; 153289 (Box 11, Folder 592)
    - Cemo, Guiseppe, 1996; 153288 (Box 11, Folder 593)
    - Chaet, Bernard, 1997-2000; 153287 (Box 11, Folder 594)
    - Christo and Jeanne Claude, 2001; 153286 (Box 11, Folder 595)
    - Chu, Ken, undated; 153285 (Box 11, Folder 596)
    - City of New York Department of Cultural Affairs., undated; 153284 (Box 11, Folder 597)
    - Clarke, Robert, 1994-1997; 153283 (Box 11, Folder 598)
    - Claudia Gian Ferrari Gallery of Contemporary Art, Milan, 1998; 153282 (Box 11, Folder 599)
    - Contemporary Arts Center [additional materials in oversize box], 1994; 153281 (Box 11, Folder 600)
    - CVI, undated; 153280 (Box 11, Folder 601)
    - D'Agostino, Roberto, undated; 153279 (Box 11, Folder 602)
    - Dance Theater Workshop, undated; 153278 (Box 11, Folder 603)
    - Desert, Ultrick, 1998; 153277 (Box 11, Folder 604)
    - Elsmlie, Kenward, 1989-1994; 153276 (Box 11, Folder 605)
    - Elovich, Richard, 1980-1981; 153275 (Box 11, Folder 606)
    - Family Correspondence to Frank, 1977-1999; 153274 (Box 11, Folder 607)
    - Fearey, Don, 1987; 153273 (Box 11, Folder 608)
    - Frame, Allen, undated; 153272 (Box 11, Folder 609)
    - Golson, 1980; 153271 (Box 11, Folder 610)
    - Gutierrez-Solana, Carlos, 1995; 153270 (Box 11, Folder 611)
    - Hall, Steven, 1981; 153269 (Box 11, Folder 612)
    - Hammond, Jane, ca. 1994; 153268 (Box 11, Folder 613)
    - Harris, Don, 1987; 153267 (Box 11, Folder 614)
    - Harris, Sarah Burt, undated; 153266 (Box 11, Folder 615)
    - Harris, William, 1995; 153265 (Box 11, Folder 616)
    - Harte, Glynn Boyd, undated; 153264 (Box 11, Folder 617)
    - Hatchondo, Anne-Marie and Michel Reilhac, 1985; 153263 (Box 11, Folder 618)
    - Hawkins, Ashton, undated; 153262 (Box 11, Folder 619)
    - Hendricks, Geoffrey, 2001; 153261 (Box 11, Folder 620)
    - HIV Related Violence Project. Found in book 672, Epidemic of Fear., undated; 153260 (Box 11, Folder 621)
    - Holzman, Eric, undated; 153259 (Box 11, Folder 622)
    - Humphrey, David, undated; 153258 (Box 11, Folder 623)
    - Independent Curators Incorporated, undated; 153257 (Box 11, Folder 624)
    - Interview Magazine, undated; 153256 (Box 11, Folder 625)
    - Iseman, Ellen, 1979; 153255 (Box 11, Folder 626)
    - Jernigan, Candy, 1988-1991; 153254 (Box 11, Folder 627)
    - Juarez, Roberto, undated; 153253 (Box 11, Folder 628)
    - Kerr, Alex, 2000; 153252 (Box 11, Folder 629)
    - Kiehl, David, 1999; 153251 (Box 11, Folder 630)
    - Knowlton, Win, 1995; 153250 (Box 11, Folder 631)
    - Korb, Carolyn, 1995; 153249 (Box 11, Folder 632)
    - Kramer, Richard, 1993; 153248 (Box 11, Folder 632A)
    - Krueck, Anstisr, 1995; 153247 (Box 11, Folder 633)
    - LaNasa, Katherine, undated; 153246 (Box 11, Folder 634)
    - LeCasble, Olivia, 1985-1998; 153245 (Box 11, Folder 635)
    - Leiber, David, 1996; 153244 (Box 11, Folder 636)
    - Leibowitz, Cary. a.k.a. Candyass [additional materials in oversize box], 1994-1995; 153243 (Box 11, Folder 637)
    - Lesbian and Gay Rights Project, 1998; 153242 (Box 11, Folder 638)
    - Lopez, Martina, 1997; 153241 (Box 11, Folder 639)
    - Maurer, Janet, 1995; 153240 (Box 11, Folder 640)
    - McCrudden, Ira, undated; 153239 (Box 11, Folder 641)
    - McCuinness, Hugh, 1993; 153238 (Box 11, Folder 642)
    - Medgar Evers College, 1995; 153237 (Box 11, Folder 643)
    - Melaney, Adam, 1995-1996; 153236 (Box 11, Folder 644)
    - Moore, Frank. Letters from Frank Moore to assorted others., undated; 153235 (Box 11, Folder 645)
    - Moore, Frank. Letters from Frank Moore to his parents., undated; 153234 (Box 11, Folder 646)
    - Moore, Patrick. Director of the Estate Project for Artists with AIDS., 1997-1998; 153233 (Box 11, Folder 647)
    - Moore, Rebecca, 1990-1998; 153232 (Box 11, Folder 648)
    - Moore, Rosalind, 1979; 153231 (Box 11, Folder 649)
    - Murray, Elizabeth, 1993; 153230 (Box 11, Folder 650)
    - Owens, Philip, 1979; 153229 (Box 11, Folder 651)
    - Pasmasambhava Buddhist Center, 1992; 153228 (Box 11, Folder 652)
    - Pamela Auchincloss Gallery, 1994; 153227 (Box 11, Folder 653)
    - Patterson, David, undated; 153226 (Box 11, Folder 654)
    - Patterson, Pat and Bob, undated; 153225 (Box 11, Folder 655)
    - Paz, Alicia, 1998; 153224 (Box 11, Folder 656)
    - Peterson, Shawn, 2001; 153223 (Box 11, Folder 657)
    - Petty, Lisa, 1987; 153222 (Box 11, Folder 658)
    - Pirmar [?], John, 1995; 153221 (Box 11, Folder 659)
    - Pozzi, Lucio, 1989; 153220 (Box 11, Folder 660)
    - Provine, Dorothy, 1990; 153219 (Box 11, Folder 661)
    - Pujol-Courmarian, Alain, 1985; 153218 (Box 11, Folder 662)
    - Reich, Frank, ca. 1977; 153217 (Box 11, Folder 663)
    - Rockman, Alexis, 1994; 153216 (Box 11, Folder 664)
    - Rowell, Patricia, 1976; 153215 (Box 11, Folder 665)
    - Sandrow, Hope, ca. 1994; 153214 (Box 11, Folder 666)
    - Sarfati, Patrick, 1980-1997; 153213 (Box 11, Folder 667)
    - Scott, Sue, 1999; 153212 (Box 11, Folder 668)
    - Self, Jim, 1983; 153211 (Box 11, Folder 669)
    - Sheridon, Laurie, ca. 1996; 153210 (Box 11, Folder 670)
    - Sillman, Amy, ca. 1994; 153209 (Box 11, Folder 671)
    - Simon, Sue, 1998; 153208 (Box 11, Folder 672)
    - Skidmore College, Tang Teaching Museum and Art Gallery., 2001; 153207 (Box 11, Folder 673)
    - Smith, Eileen, 1994; 153206 (Box 11, Folder 674)
    - Sperone Westwater, undated; 153205 (Box 11, Folder 675)
    - Stanton, Todd, undated; 153204 (Box 11, Folder 676)
    - Stefantos, Maria Elena, undated; 153203 (Box 11, Folder 677)
    - Strompf, Steve, 1998; 153202 (Box 11, Folder 678)
    - Taylor, Steed, ca. 1995; 153201 (Box 11, Folder 679)
    - Teruko, Kiyoshi, undated; 153200 (Box 11, Folder 680)
    - Tisa, Ken, undated; 153199 (Box 11, Folder 681)
    - Traglio, Carlo, 1995; 153198 (Box 11, Folder 682)
    - Visual AIDS, 1997-2001; 153197 (Box 11, Folder 683)
    - Warner, Michael, 1994; 153196 (Box 11, Folder 684)
    - Warren, Rosanna, 1975-2000; 153195 (Box 11, Folder 685)
    - Webster, Stephen, 1981-1986; 153194 (Box 11, Folder 686)
    - Wemega-Kwawo, Rikki, 1998; 153193 (Box 11, Folder 687)
    - Werthmann, Colleen, undated; 153192 (Box 11, Folder 688)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1996-2002; 153191 (Box 11, Folder 689)
    - Wilson, Robert, 1985-1999; 153190 (Box 11, Folder 690)
    - Winslow, Kirk, 1977; 153189 (Box 11, Folder 691)
    - Wood, Suzy Mallory, 1981; 153188 (Box 11, Folder 692)
    - Woodruff, Tom, undated; 153187 (Box 11, Folder 693)
    - Young, Virgil, 1981; 153186 (Box 11, Folder 694)
  - Subseries B: First Name Only, 153147
    - Barry, 1987-1988; 153184 (Box 11, Folder 695)
    - Betsy, 1992-1998; 153183 (Box 11, Folder 696)
    - Bobby R., 1995-1997; 153182 (Box 11, Folder 697)
    - Brad, 1978; 153181 (Box 11, Folder 698)
    - Bro-bro, undated; 153180 (Box 11, Folder 699)
    - Buzz, 1995-1997; 153179 (Box 11, Folder 700)
    - Carlos, 1989-1996; 153178 (Box 11, Folder 701)
    - Cecile and Steve, 1989-1996; 153177 (Box 11, Folder 702)
    - Coco, 1982-1986; 153176 (Box 11, Folder 703)
    - D., ca. 1983; 153175 (Box 11, Folder 704)
    - Dennis, 1994; 153174 (Box 11, Folder 705)
    - Elain, undated; 153173 (Box 11, Folder 706)
    - Fred, ca. 2001; 153172 (Box 11, Folder 707)
    - Gaby, undated; 153171 (Box 11, Folder 708)
    - George, 1978-1988; 153170 (Box 11, Folder 709)
    - Gladys, 1994; 153169 (Box 11, Folder 710)
    - Hamey, 1995; 153168 (Box 11, Folder 711)
    - Heys, undated; 153167 (Box 11, Folder 712)
    - Jan, 1980-1997; 153166 (Box 11, Folder 713)
    - Jim, 1983-1991; 153165 (Box 11, Folder 714)
    - John, 1998; 153164 (Box 11, Folder 715)
    - Kynaston, 1975-1977; 153163 (Box 11, Folder 716)
    - L., 1977-1987; 153162 (Box 11, Folder 717)
    - Laurie, 1975-1981; 153161 (Box 11, Folder 718)
    - Liz, ca. 1993; 153160 (Box 11, Folder 719)
    - Mara Jayne, ca. 1996; 153159 (Box 11, Folder 720)
    - Marc, 1991-1994; 153158 (Box 11, Folder 721)
    - Mario, 1974-1976; 153157 (Box 11, Folder 722)
    - Martha, 1995; 153156 (Box 11, Folder 723)
    - Michael and Robert, 1983-1994; 153155 (Box 11, Folder 724)
    - Nancy, 1991-1993; 153154 (Box 11, Folder 725)
    - Phil and Martha, 1991; 153153 (Box 11, Folder 726)
    - Pierre, 1978-1983; 153152 (Box 11, Folder 727)
    - Policewoman, ca. 1992; 153151 (Box 11, Folder 728)
    - Shawn, undated; 153150 (Box 11, Folder 729)
    - Sophie, 1985-1990; 153149 (Box 11, Folder 730)
    - Tom, undated; 153148 (Box 11, Folder 731)
  - Subseries C: Miscellaneous, Illegible and Unsigned, 153143
    - Miscellaneous, illegible or unsigned correspondence, undated; 153146 (Box 12, Folder 732)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042232507
    - Miscellaneous, illegible or unsigned correspondence, undated; 153145 (Box 12, Folder 733)
    - Miscellaneous, illegible or unsigned correspondence, undated; 153144 (Box 12, Folder 734)
  - Subseries D: Manuscripts, 153141
    - "Vajrachedicka Prajnaparamita [sic] The Diamond cutter wisdom that has gone beyond, or, the Diamond Sutra." handwritten., undated; 153142 (Box 12, Folder 735)
- Series IV: Source Material, 152961
  This series contains seven subseries; Subseries A: magazines, Subseries B: catalogues, Subseries C: images, Subseries D: articles, Subseries E: photographs, Subseries F: books and Subseries G: ephemera. These materials served as research, inspiration and models for Frank Moore's artwork. Where possible, materials are organized alphabetically by author or title.
  - Subseries A: Magazines, 153128
    - American Horticulturalist, June 1995, 153139 (Box 12, Folder 736)
    - Item removed to oversize, 153138 (Box 12, Folder 737)
    - Item removed to oversize, 1995-1996; 153137 (Box 12, Folder 738)
    - Hunter Trader Trapper. volume 46 number 4, July 1923, 153136 (Box 12, Folder 739)
    - International Wildlife. volume 13 number 6, November-December 1983, 153135 (Box 12, Folder 740)
    - National Geographic. volume 184 number 4, October 1993., 153134 (Box 12, Folder 741)
    - National Geographic. Volume 185 number 2, February 1994, 153133 (Box 12, Folder 742)
    - Nest: A Quarterly of Interiors. Spring 2001, 153132 (Box 12, Folder 743)
    - New York Times Magazine. January 30, 2000., 153131 (Box 12, Folder 744)
    - U.S. News and World Report. March 25, 1991, 153130 (Box 12, Folder 745)
    - WIRED. February 2001., 153129 (Box 12, Folder 746)
  - Subseries B: Catalogues and Manuals, 153113
    - Item removed to oversize, 198684 (Box 12, Folder 747)
    - Dover Antiques and Photography, undated; 153127 (Box 12, Folder 748)
    - Dujardin Machines, undated; 153126 (Box 12, Folder 749)
    - Gordon Novelty Co. Inc. Catalogue, 1982; 153125 (Box 12, Folder 750)
    - The Gulf Specimen Co., undated; 153124 (Box 12, Folder 751)
    - Jones and Scully Inc. Orchidglade, 1969-1970; 153123 (Box 12, Folder 752)
    - Lakeland Nursery Catalogue, 1983; 153122 (Box 12, Folder 753)
    - Manny's Millinery Supply Co. Spring 1991., 153121 (Box 12, Folder 754)
    - Regina Twinbrush Floor Polisher and Scrubber: Instructions and Care, undated; 153120 (Box 12, Folder 755)